icrimewatch.net 2016-05-31

# Privacy - WatchSystems

**Privacy**

Watch Systems has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your personal privacy rights. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:[www.WatchSystems.com](http://www.watchsystems.com/)

This privacy statement reflects Watch Systems’ current practices and will be updated as necessary to reflect future changes.

**Watch Systems’  privacy philosophy **  
We recognize that the tremendous benefits afforded users of the Internet are vastly reduced if the individual’s privacy is compromised through the misuse of personal information. Watch Systems is therefore committed to ensuring that you are in control of how your personal information is collected and how it is used.

Our philosophy is based on the assumption that any personal information that we receive through this site will be collected through an explicit opt-in process where the you, the user, explicitly grant us the right to collect that information for clearly identified purposes. We are committed to maintaining your right to remove your personal information from our records at any time through an easily exercised opt-out process.

Additional information about Internet-related personal privacy issues is available from the Federal Trade Commission at: <http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/>

**Information collection and use  **  
Watch Systems collects and maintains your personal information in the following ways: Name, company name, address, phone, fax, company URL, e-mail address and comments may be collected when you request to download content or choose to contact us via the inquiry form on the site. This information is used to follow up with your inquiry, alert you to future content that may be of interest and allow us to create new content that is most relevant to you.

Your personal contact information is collected when you contact us via the address, phone or fax numbers, or e-mail addresses listed on this site. We use this information to follow up with you on your individual requests. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of information written to a file on your computer by a Web server. Cookies are typically employed by Web site designers to improve the user’s experience on the site.

Watch Systems currently uses cookies on this site within our ‘Downloads’ sections. It is our intent that this site will always continue to function properly for anyone choosing to reject the use of cookies.

More detailed information about cookies can be found at Cookie Central: [http://www.cookiecentral.com/](http://www.cookiecentral.com/%20)

**Security**  
Watch System has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Based on industry standard best practices, these security measures protect you from unauthorized access of the personal information that you have chosen to share with us. We will never share your personal information with third parties unless you have given us explicit permission to do so. 

**Log files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information.   
**  
Linked Web sites  **  
Watch Systems has no control over the privacy policies of other sites we may include links to within this site. We encourage you to review the posted privacy policies of these sites where available. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Watch Systems never knowingly collects personal information from children. If we ever become aware that we have personal information on a child we will delete it immediately. Watch Systems encourages parents to go online with their children. Information that can help parents to teach their children to use the Internet safely can be found at the Internet Safety Site: <http://www.safekids.com/index.html>

**Policy updates**  
Changes to our privacy policy will be posted here and via email to users who have elected to opt-in. We intend that you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users will always have a choice as to whether or not to allow us to continue to use their information.

Last update: September 2015

**Legal  **  
© Copyright Watch Systems, LLC 2003 – 2008. All Rights Reserved.

4093 Total Views  9 Views Today
